Name: Erick Saasen

Contact Information

Phone: 208-659-8598

Gmail: escastle.designs@gmail.com

Summary

I am an energetic young person with a drive for excellence and integrity. I take direction well and commit to handling whatever may be asked of me as quickly as possible. I work well with others, am honest, hardworking, and have a service-oriented character. I enjoy fast-paced team-oriented environments filled with challenges and opportunities.

Skills

- Technical Skills: UX Research, Wireframing, Prototyping, Usability Testing, UI Design, HTML, CSS, JS
- **Soft Skills:** Managerial experience in the trades & on my teams in all sports, good with others, shows initiative, Hard Working, Ambitious, Self Learner
- Certifications: UX/UI Certificate

Experience

Junior Carpenter

Castle Rock Construction — Coeur D' Alene, ID & Spokane WA Framing, Siding, Carpentry, etc.

April 2016 - October 2021

- Lead clean up crews
- Wrapped up jobs on my own

Finisher/Junior Foreman

Three Sons Concrete — Coeur D' Alene, ID Concrete foundations, Slabs, etc.

October 2021 – Present

Being molded to become a foreman for the company. This includes:

- Leading a crew to go to wrap up foundation walls
- Pour flatwork on my own
- Running errands
- Calling contractors

Education

Associates of Science

North Idaho College — Coeur d' Alene, ID August, 2020 – May 13th, 2023

UX/UI Certificate

Careerfoundry — Remote November, 2023 – November, 2024

Additional Sections (if applicable)

- Languages: Fluent in English, Spanish Beginner
- Hobbies/Interests:
 - Sports Basketball, Football, etc.
 - o Outdoors -Fishing, Dirt Biking, Kayaking, etc.
 - o Learning New languages, Reading, History, etc.